The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you.
You may be seated. Thank you.
Hallelujah.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Yes, we have seen the presence of God.
It is always like that in the climate in the presence of God.
You can see the climate.
You see the move where God is present.
The Bible says in the Book of John 10:34-35,
'If you call them gods from whom the Word of God came - the Scripture cannot be broken'.
The question: How do we know a man of God?
We know a man of God by the words he speaks.
The words he speaks represent his heart's desire.
Are you with me?
"Let there be light!" - and there is light. That is a man of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Take note: If the Word is not according to the Spirit of God,
it will remain meaningless, idle and oftentimes destructive.
Are you with me?
If the Word is not according to (the Spirit of God) -
because we shall be judged by the Word we (speak).
If the Word is not according to the truth of the Gospel, according to the Spirit of God,
the Word will remain meaningless and oftentimes destructive.
Remember what happened to the seven sons of Sceva.
That is what is happening to many of us:
If the words you speak are not according to God's Spirit,
because it is God's Spirit that reveals Jesus.
It is God's Spirit that makes the Word work.
The Word becomes a tool.
If the Word is not according to the Spirit of the Father,
it will remain idle, meaningless and oftentimes dangerous.
If you say 'Jesus' and the 'Jesus' you called is not according to the Spirit of God,
satan will ask you, "By what authority? Who are you?"
We have seen the true Gospel today.
We need to know the faithfulness and trustworthiness of God.
You have seen it; you have realised that God is reliable.
If I'm talking to you?
How many of us have realised that God is reliable?
I can't see your hand.
If you have realised that God is reliable, what else again?
Your faith will simultaneously grow.
Your love for Christ will simultaneously grow.
Your desire for Christ will simultaneously - side by side - lift up.
If your faith has grown today, let me see your hand.
Your faith, your love for Christ - so much!
Let me see your hand.
Your desire for Christ!
Hallelujah.
That is the work of the Holy Spirit.
Before we can repent, however, conviction must come.
Every day you get closer to God by the power of repentance.
The Bible says repentance is the greatest gift from God.
Repentance is possibly our greatest gift from God - that is conviction.
Conviction must come.
Conviction is the awakening of your conscience to the truth.
You and I have seen that God is the same yesterday, today and forever.
Do you know that God is greater than you and your problems?
Do you know that?
I can't hear you!
[Yes!]
That is conviction.
Before you can repent, however, conviction must come.
Conviction is the awakening of your conscience to the truth.
"Ah, I need to go and read my Bible again."
"Ah, I thought I have read, I have finished Genesis to Revelation."
"Ah, I thought I know the Bible."
"Ah, I thought I'm a prayer warrior."
"Ah, I thought I know God."
"Ah, I thought I live in the wilderness."
"Ah, I need to go and read my Bible again."
"Again and again."
Awakening of your conscience to the truth.
What is the next thing now? Ask yourself.
Concerning God.
Ask yourself, "What is the next thing concerning God?"
Ask yourself, "What is the next thing for me concerning God?"
The best answer for anyone of us is: I'm still a baby.
I need to know more.
"So, God can be so real?"
That is one of the questions you ask yourself.
"God can be so real?"
God is great.
Hallelujah.
God is great. That is God for you.
TT: Mel Flowers 28/12/2018
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 03/01/2019